anomalousmaterial.com 2012-12-11

# Privacy Policy — ANOMALOUS MATERIAL

Anomalous Material is fully committed to protect your private information and will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in the following Privacy Policy. This page will explain AnomalousMaterial.com, (“Anomalous Material”) information-gathering and dissemination practices for our website: www.anomalousmaterial.com (the “Site”).

### Information We Collect

Anomalous Material automatically collects certain technical information about each visitor, such as IP address, Internet Service Provider (ISP), general geographic location and browser information when you connect on the Site. This information is only used as an aggregate to track visiting patterns and provide a better visitor experience. This information may also be provided in the aggregate to third parties, including advertisers, to describe basic use patterns for the Site, but this information is never linked to any personally identifiable information.

Anomalous Material may also use Cookies to provide an optimal user’s experience on the site and does not share this information with any third party. For example, cookies help your browser remember your preferences to better enhance you experience on our Site.

Additionally, personally identifiable information may be collected on Anomalous Material when you choose to contact us, leave a comment, enter a contest or use one of the social network options. This information is used solely so we can interact with you and is not shared with any third party.

While we will never intentionally disclose individually identifiable information to any third party without your permission, Anomalous Material reserves the right to cooperate fully with local, state and federal law enforcement authorities in respect of any lawful request to disclose your identity or other information in respect of your posting any materials which violate any applicable or relevant law. We may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement personnel, government officials, or others when we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent violations of the law, injury to person or property, or any harm to this Site or others.

### Links

Anomalous Material contains links to third-party websites, such as other media websites, advertisers and other content providers. By clicking on any of these links, you are leaving Anomalous Material and this Privacy Policy will no longer apply. Anomalous Material cannot guarantee your privacy outside of its premise and this Site assumes no liability for any practices made on other websites we link to.

### Third Party Advertising

Anomalous Material uses the services of several ad networks, including IndieClick for serving ads and marketing campaigns when you visit this Site. Through the use of cookies and pixel tags, these companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide customized advertisements on this Site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you’d like to learn more about these practices and/or would like to opt out, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Anomalous Material is participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. You may see the “Ad Choices” link within advertising units displayed on this Site. These links will redirect you to [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) where you can learn more about Online Behavorial Advertising and have the option to opt out.

### Children Under 13

Anomalous Material takes the safety and privacy of children very importantly. In that regard, this Site is intended for use by adult and teenagers older than 13. Parents should review this privacy policy and ensure that children under 13 must not submit any personally identifiable information.

### Acceptance of These Terms

Your continued use of this Site under the application of this Privacy Policy signifies your agreement with this document. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please refrain from visiting Anomalous Material.

### Modifications to this Privacy Policy

Anomalous Material reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Visitors are advised to review this document periodically.

© 2008-2012, AnomalousMaterial.com
